<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Be True</title>
	<atom:link href="http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php</link>
	<description>Thank you for reading fresh news</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 22:01:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sony announces Selena Gomez&#8217;s &#8216;The Broken Hearts Gallery&#8217; to make theatrical debut this summer</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 17:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Без рубрики]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN)Sony is banking on moviegoers heading back to theaters this summer. The film studio announced Tuesday that they are releasing &#8220;The Broken Hearts Gallery&#8221; in theaters on July 10. This is the first major theatrical release from the studio in the wake of the coronavirus pandemic. The movie, which is executive produced by Selena Gomez, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN)Sony is banking on moviegoers heading back to theaters this summer.</p>
<p>The film studio announced Tuesday that they are releasing &#8220;The Broken Hearts Gallery&#8221; in theaters on July 10. This is the first major theatrical release from the studio in the wake of the coronavirus pandemic.<br />
The movie, which is executive produced by Selena Gomez, stars Geraldine Viswanathan, Dacre Montgomery, Utkarsh Ambudkar, Molly Gordon, Phillipa Soo, Suki Waterhouse, Arturo Castro, Ego Nwodim, Taylor Hill and Bernadette Peters. It marks the directorial debut of Natalie Krinsky.<br />
&#8220;Hearing from more female writers and directors is very much needed,&#8221; Gomez said in a statement. &#8220;Natalie is a wonderful talent and I am happy to be a part of her debut film. I understand people&#8217;s concerns regarding returning to activities we all loved prior to COVID-19. I hope everyone will listen to scientists&#8217; recommendations and consider others&#8217; health and safety while enjoying the movie theater experience.&#8221;<br />
July marks a big moment for the film industry. Some of the most anticipated films of the year including Disney&#8217;s live-action &#8220;Mulan,&#8221; Warner Brother&#8217;s &#8220;Tenet&#8221; and Russell Crowe&#8217;s &#8220;Unhinged&#8221; will all hit theaters.<br />
AMC plans to reopen its theaters in July<br />
AMC plans to reopen its theaters in July<br />
But the big question remains, will people still want to sit in theaters as Covid-19 hotspots continue to pop up across the country?<br />
AMC Theatres, the world&#8217;s largest theater chain said in a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission last week that they have &#8220;substantial doubt&#8221; they can remain in business after closing locations across the globe due to the pandemic. But in its first quarter earnings report Tuesday they said they plan to open their 1,000 locations across the world in July. AMC declined to comment for this story.<br />
Related: At these movie theaters, the shows have gone on despite the coronavirus pandemic<br />
The Chairman of Sony&#8217;s Motion Picture Group, Tom Rothman, told CNN in a recent interview that he remains optimistic.<br />
&#8220;A joy that comes when you see it in darkened theater with a bunch of people and you laugh and you cry,&#8221; Rothman said. &#8220;Actually in the long term, I&#8217;m very, very optimistic, but I do not underestimate the short term obstacles, which are significant.&#8221;<br />
The announcement of Sony&#8217;s &#8220;Broken Hearts Gallery&#8221; release comes after the news of the sale of their Tom Hanks movie, &#8220;Greyhound&#8221; to Apple TV+ due to the pandemic.<br />
&#8220;Instead of pushing [&#8216;Greyhound&#8217;] well into next year, there were many streamers who were very avid for it, and Apple was extremely excited about it,&#8221; Rothman said. &#8220;Apple was a really, really good home for that particular film. In the case of &#8216;Greyhound,&#8217; making a deal with Apple made sense, but that is not our overall business.&#8221;<br />
Some film distributors are pivoting in the midst of the pandemic. Berry Meyerowitz, the president of film distributor Quiver, said he and his team made the decision to switch up their strategy when it came to the release of their Kevin James thriller, &#8220;Becky&#8221; by securing over 40 drive-in theaters across the country, along with streaming and on-demand.<br />
&#8220;We feel like we&#8217;re giving consumers and the audience the best of both worlds as they can,&#8221; he said. &#8220;If they&#8217;re close to one of the drive-ins to go see it there, which is just an amazing nostalgic experience, but also if they&#8217;re not close to a drive-in or would rather watch it at home, they can sit on their couch, download the film and have that amazing experience from the comfort of their home.&#8221;<br />
But Rothman is adamant that the future of moviegoing in the traditional sense will be back.<br />
&#8220;In the fifties, they said that television would kill movies. And then in the seventies that VHS would kill movies. And then in the eighties that the 300 channel cable television would kill movies. And now they stated that streaming would come and kill movies,&#8221; he said. &#8220;Let me tell you something, nothing will kill movies.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>These films don&#8217;t help the racism conversation</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/croatia-met-the-national-team-after-the-final-of-the-2018-world-cup/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/croatia-met-the-national-team-after-the-final-of-the-2018-world-cup/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 17:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN)The world feels different right now and content is being viewed through a different lens. With conversation in our culture focused on systematic racism and the treatment of black people after the death of George Floyd while in the custody of Minneapolis police, some are reevaluating Hollywood&#8217;s on-screen depictions of racism. And we have to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN)The world feels different right now and content is being viewed through a different lens.</p>
<p>With conversation in our culture focused on systematic racism and the treatment of black people after the death of George Floyd while in the custody of Minneapolis police, some are reevaluating Hollywood&#8217;s on-screen depictions of racism.<br />
And we have to tell you, some of them have not aged well.<br />
On the heels of the news that HBO Max has pulled &#8220;Gone with the Wind&#8221; to add &#8220;historical context,&#8221; here are a few films that probably aren&#8217;t the most helpful if you are trying to learn more about race and racism:<br />
&#8220;The Help&#8221; (2011)<br />
Twitter was seething after the film directed by Tate Taylor and based on the same named 2009 novel written by Kathryn Stockett started trending as protests sprung up following Floyd&#8217;s death.<br />
There were concerns even before the movie was released.</p>
<p>Partly because Taylor is a white man, who was tasked with shepherding a story about a pair of black maids, Aibileen Clark (played by Viola Davis) and Minny Jackson (played by Octavia Spencer), set in Jackson, Mississippi during the Civil Rights Movement.<br />
Those voices grew louder after the film hit theaters, as many complained that it focused more on the white character of Eugenia &#8220;Skeeter&#8221; Phelan (played by Emma Stone).<br />
And while her performance won Spencer a best supporting actress Oscar, Davis has since said she regrets taking the role.<br />
&#8220;I just felt that at the end of the day that it wasn&#8217;t the voices of the maids that were heard,&#8221; Davis told the New York Times in 2018.<br />
Earlier this week, Bryce Dallas Howard, who played Hilly Holbrook in &#8220;The Help,&#8221; suggested ten other films to consider viewing to better learn about America&#8217;s history of racial inequity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/croatia-met-the-national-team-after-the-final-of-the-2018-world-cup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8216;Gone with the Wind&#8217; reignites debate as Hollywood wrestles with its history</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/startup_ukr/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/startup_ukr/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 16:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN)&#8221;Gone with the Wind&#8221; remains the highest-grossing movie of all time when adjusted for inflation and won 10 Oscars, including the first ever for an African-American performer, supporting actress Hattie McDaniel. The 1939 movie &#8212; adapted from Margaret Mitchell&#8217;s bestselling novel set during the Civil War &#8212; also contains numerous problematic elements that haven&#8217;t aged [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN)&#8221;Gone with the Wind&#8221; remains the highest-grossing movie of all time when adjusted for inflation and won 10 Oscars, including the first ever for an African-American performer, supporting actress Hattie McDaniel.</p>
<p>The 1939 movie &#8212; adapted from Margaret Mitchell&#8217;s bestselling novel set during the Civil War &#8212; also contains numerous problematic elements that haven&#8217;t aged well, from stereotyped depictions of African Americans to the debate over whether the staircase scene between Rhett and Scarlett, which concludes off screen, was a case of marital rape.<br />
&#8220;Gone with the Wind&#8221; is the latest movie to face renewed concerns about its exposure in the 21st century, as studios mine their libraries to stock the shelves of new streaming services. The controversy over that erupted again this week, as HBO Max, the new service from CNN parent WarnerMedia, announced that it was temporarily pulling the movie from its rotation.<br />
The film will return, a spokesperson said, with &#8220;a discussion of its historical context&#8221; and denunciation of its racially charged aspects. The movie itself won&#8217;t be altered.<br />
The announcement followed a Los Angeles Times oped by filmmaker John Ridley, who noted that the film &#8220;glorifies the antebellum south&#8221; and perpetuates &#8220;some of the most painful stereotypes of people of color.&#8221;<br />
Disney has already publicly wrestled with these issues in launching its streaming service, Disney+, opting not to include the 1946 film &#8220;Song of the South,&#8221; another title that romanticized the old South. Disney+ has made other movies available, such as &#8220;Dumbo,&#8221; with a disclaimer that reads, &#8220;This program is presented as originally created. It may contain outdated cultural depictions.&#8221;<br />
Seeking to contextualize old films is not a new issue for WarnerMedia. The company&#8217;s stable of cable networks includes Turner Classic Movies, which presents such films with hosts who introduce and discuss them.<br />
Hattie McDaniel won an Oscar for &#39;Gone With the Wind.&#39;<br />
Hattie McDaniel won an Oscar for &#8216;Gone With the Wind.&#8217;<br />
The specific debate over &#8220;Gone with the Wind&#8221; is hardly a new one either, but as HBO Max noted, it comes at a moment when the United States is again grappling with its history on the subject of race &#8212; and how those attitudes filtered through the culture and entertainment of the times. Notably, the new Netflix series &#8220;Hollywood&#8221; zeroes in on that topic, with McDaniel &#8212; who was segregated from her white co-stars at the Academy Awards &#8212; featured as a minor character within the fictionalized retelling.<br />
The questions surrounding &#8220;Gone with the Wind&#8221; actually predated the film. Debate immediately ensued over the 1936 publication of Mitchell&#8217;s novel, with its nostalgia for plantation life, portrayal of happy slaves and threatening freed blacks, and sympathy toward the Confederate cause.<br />
As the Washington Post&#8217;s Alyssa Rosenberg noted, even McDaniel&#8217;s award-winning performance &#8220;couldn&#8217;t wholly transcend the trope of a loyal slave who rejects freedom and prefers to serve her former owners.&#8221;<br />
Weighing the movie&#8217;s negatives versus its merits &#8212; including Vivien Leigh&#8217;s portrayal of the iconic heroine Scarlett O&#8217;Hara &#8212; Rosenberg concluded it is &#8220;the one Confederate monument worth saving.&#8221;<br />
The discussion of what to do with movies like &#8220;Gone with the Wind&#8221; arose again in 2017, when a theater in Memphis, Tenn., opted to drop it from a screening series after the Unite the Right rally in Charlottesville, Va.<br />
&#8220;You can&#8217;t sweep history under the rug,&#8221; USC professor of media and cinema studies Todd Boyd told the Los Angeles Times at the time, adding. &#8220;But it&#8217;s important to have context whenever you&#8217;re viewing material of this kind. Otherwise, people can embrace and celebrate it without dealing with the whole truth.&#8221;<br />
That process can be messy, and it inevitably invites criticism &#8212; especially from conservatives eager to portray Hollywood liberals as bowing to calls for censorship. Accused of insensitivity in the past, it&#8217;s possible to engage in what can look like overreactions in the present.<br />
But there&#8217;s a difference between context and censorship. If the best answer to potentially offensive speech or art is more speech or art, facilitating a broader conversation about a classic like &#8220;Gone with the Wind&#8221; &#8212; which is a far cry from sweeping it away &#8212; represents a reasonable solution.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/startup_ukr/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
